# Nikhil Dindorkar (1) Featured

Software Engineer seeking assignment in Software Development, Software Application Development, Project Management, Requirement Gathering, Software design, Web development, Core Java, Spring, Hibernate, JPA, JAX-RS, Spring Scheduler, Angular JS, Eclipse, Maven, SVN



Current Designation: Software Engineer Total Experience: 4 Year(s) 3 Month(s)

Current Company: DXC Technology Notice Period: Currently Serving Notice Period

Current Location: Indore Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Computer Science]

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Mumbai, Pune Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Software Engineer, Software Development, Project Management, Requirement Gathering, Software design, Web development, Core Java, Spring, Hibernate, JPA, JAX-RS, Spring

Scheduler, Angular JS, Eclipse, Maven, SVN

Verified: Email - id Phone Number |

Last Active: 21-Jan-21 Last Modified: 21-Jan-21

#### Summary

Motivated Software Engineer who exceeds goals, with 3.4+ years of experience.

Other Skills: Software Development, Software Application Development, Project Management, Requirement Gathering, Software design, Web development, Core Java, Spring, Hibernate, JPA, JAX-RS, Spring Scheduler, Angular JS, Eclipse, Maven, SVN

### **Work Experience**

**DXC Technology** as Software Engineer

Feb 2020 to Till Date

Innoeye Technologies Pvt. Ltd as Software Engineer

Sep 2016 to Jan 2020

**PROJECTS** 

Innoeye Business Intelligence Platform January 2018 - 10 January 2020

Developing platform to facilitate the creation of dashboards by supplying data in the form of tables and relations.

Focused on modules - chart designer and dashboard designer

Technologies Used: Core Java, Spring, Hibernate, JPA, JAX-RS, Spring Scheduler, Angular JS.

E-Points January 2017 - January 2018

Loyalty based E-Commerce application with features like Reward Transaction, Activating gift card, Redeeming reward points etc.

Contributed in individual capacity in developing transactions - activate gift card and redemption of reward points Designed application used by POS (Point of Sale) machines to perform financial transactions using Java based socket connection.

Technologies Used: Core Java, Spring, Hibernate, JPA, JAX-RS, Spring Scheduler, Angular JS.

## **Education**

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computer Science) from Swami Vivekanand College of Engineering, Indore in 2016

#### IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used Experience
Core Java,JavaEE	
Servlet,JSP,JAX-RS, JAX-B	
Spring 3.0,Hibernate,	
Spring Restful Web Services	
MySQL	
Apache Tomcat	
AngularJs 1.5 , javascript , Jquery,AJAX	
JSON	
Eclipse, Maven, SVN	

#### **Affirmative Action**

**Work Authorization** 

Physically Challenged: No

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time